CASSIE LEE

Software Engineer

ABOUT ME

I am a junior software engineer who has a passion for creating user-friendly applications. I am a strong team player and I have gained excellent cross-functional teamwork skills through my previous varied work experiences in the field of healthcare and entertainment.

TECH SKILLS

- HTML, CSS, Bootstrap
- Javascript, jQuery
- Ruby on Rails
- Ajax
- React.js
- Node.js
- MongoDB
- SQL

CONTACT

Email: cassielee8757@gmail.com

Phone: 0412 833 961

Github: github.com/casslee8757 LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/cassielee1

PROJECTS

CaseBOOK

- A social network app where you can post information, images, leave comments and like/unlike posts.
- MERN, CSS

Spy-Fall clone

- A social deception game where you aim to find the 'imposter' hidden amongst the players.
- React.js, Rails

Movie Search Website

- A movie search website where the user can write a review and rate the movie. Additionally, the user can save and delete the movies in the wish list.
- CRUD system on Ruby-on-Rails, CSS, Javascript

Tic-Tac-Toe

- Tic-Tac-Toe game with 2 different game modes. In the singleplayer mode, you can play the game with Al and in the multiplayer mode, you can enjoy the game with a friend.
- HTML, CSS, Javascript, ¡Query

EXPERIENCE

Part-time Medical Receptionist

Myhealth Wentworth Point

Jul 2018 - Dec 2021

- Assisted management in rolling out 200 COVID-19 vaccines a day during the peak of the pandemic in Sydney.
- Collaborated with IT team to handle technical issues within the clinic

VIP Casino Dealer

The Star

Jan 2015 - Aug 2017

- Developed excellent cross teamwork skills through collaborating within a team of 10 to provide a strong customer experience for VIP guests.
- Delivered efficient and accurate operation of the games to diverse international guests.

EDUCATION

Software Engineering Immersive

General Assembly Dec 2021 - Mar 2022

Bachelor of Medical Science

Macquarie University Feb 2019 - Nov 2021